By RentAnAdviser.com
Look
If you had
One shot
Or one opportunity
To seize everything you ever wanted
In one moment
Would you capture it
Or just let it slip?
Yo
His palms are sweaty‚ knees
weak‚ arms are heavy
There′s vomit on his sweater
already‚ mom′s spaghetti
He is nervous‚ but on the surface
he looks calm and ready
To drop bombs‚ but he
keeps on forgettin′
What he wrote down‚ the whole
crowd goes so loud
He opens his mouth‚ but the
words won′t come out
He is chokin′‚ how‚ everybody′s
jokin′ now
The clocks run out‚ times
up‚ over‚ blaow!
Snap back to reality‚ oh
there goes gravity
Oh‚ there goes Rabbit‚ he choked
He is so mad‚ but he won′t
give up that easy? No
He won′t have it‚ he knows his
whole back city′s ropes
It don′t matter‚ He is dope‚ he
knows that‚ but He is broke
He is so stacked that he knows‚
when he goes back to his mobile
home‚ that′s when it is
Back to the lab again yo‚
this whole rhapsody
He better go capture this moment
and hope it don′t pass him
You better lose yourself in
the music‚ the moment
You own it‚ you better never let it go
You only get one shot‚ do not
miss your chance to blow
This opportunity comes once
in a lifetime you better
You better lose yourself in
the music‚ the moment
You own it‚ you better never let it go
You only get one shot‚ do not
miss your chance to blow
This opportunity comes once
in a lifetime you better
The souls escaping‚ through this
hole that it is gaping
This world is mine for the taking
Make me king‚ as we move toward
a‚ new world order
A normal life is borin′‚ but super
stardom′s close to post mortem
It only grows harder‚
only grows hotter
He blows us all over these
hoes is all on him
Coast to coast shows‚ He is
known as the globetrotter
Lonely roads‚ God only knows‚
He is grown farther from
home‚ He is no father
He goes home and barely knows
his own daughter
But hold your nose ′cause here
goes the cold water
His hoes don′t want him no
mo‚ He is cold product
They moved on to the next schmo who
flows‚ he nose dove and sold nada
So the soap opera is told and unfolds‚
I suppose It is old partna‚
but the beat goes on
Da da dumb da dumb da da
You better lose yourself in
the music‚ the moment
You own it‚ you better never let it go
You only get one shot‚ do not
miss your chance to blow
This opportunity comes once
in a lifetime you better
You better lose yourself in
the music‚ the moment
You own it‚ you better never let it go
You only get one shot‚ do not
miss your chance to blow
This opportunity comes once
in a lifetime you better
No more games‚ I am a change
what you call rage
Tear this motherfuckin roof
off like two dogs caged
I was playin′ in the beginnin′‚
the mood all changed
I been chewed up and spit
out and booed off stage
But I kept rhymin′ and stepwritin′
the next cipher
Best believe somebody′s
payin′ the pied piper
All the pain inside amplified by the
Fact that I can′t get
by with my nine to
Five and I can′t provide
the right type of
Life for my family ′cause man‚
these God damn food stamps
don′t buy diapers
And it is no movie‚ there′s
no Mekhi Phifer
This is my life and these
times are so hard
And It is getting even harder tryin′
to feed and water my seed‚ plus
See dishonor caught up between bein′
a father and a prima dona
Baby mama drama screamin′
on and too much
For me to want to say in one
spot‚ another jam or not
Has gotten me to the point‚ I
am like a snail I have got
To formulate a plot fore I
end up in jail or shot
Success is my only motherfuckin
option‚ failures not
Mom‚ I love you‚ but this trail
has got to go‚ I cannot grow
old in Salthems lot
So here I go is my shot
Feet fail me not ′cause maybe the
only opportunity that I got
You better lose yourself in
the music‚ the moment
You own it‚ you better never let it go
You only get one shot‚ do not
miss your chance to blow
This opportunity comes once
in a lifetime you better
You better lose yourself in
the music‚ the moment
You own it‚ you better never let it go
You only get one shot‚ do not
miss your chance to blow
This opportunity comes once
in a lifetime you better
You can do anything you
set your mind to‚ man
By RentAnAdviser.com