By RentAnAdviser.com
I have paid my dues
Time after time
I have done my sentence
But committed no crime
And bad mistakes
I have made a few
I have had my share of sand
kicked in my face
But I have come through
(And I need just go on and
on‚ and on‚ and on)
We are the champions‚ my friends
And we′ll keep on fighting
′til the end
We are the champions
No time for losers
′Cause we are the champions
of the world
I have taken my bows
And my curtain calls
You brought me fame and fortune‚ and
everything that goes with it
I thank you all
But It is been no bed of roses
No pleasure cruise
I consider it a challenge before
the whole human race
And I ain′t gona lose
(And I need just go on and
on‚ and on‚ and on)
We are the champions‚ my friends
And we′ll keep on fighting
′til the end
We are the champions
No time for losers
′Cause we are the champions
of the world
We are the champions‚ my friends
And we′ll keep on fighting
′til the end
We are the champions
No time for losers
′Cause we are the champions
By RentAnAdviser.com