by RentAnAdviser.com
I am at a party I don′t wanna be at
And I don′t ever wear a
suit and tie‚ yeah
Wonderin′ if I could
sneak out the back
Nobody′s even lookin′ me in my eyes
Can you take my hand?
Finish my drink‚ say‚ Shall
we dance? (Hell‚ yeah)
You know I love ya‚ did
I ever tell ya?
You make it better like that
Don′t think I fit in at this party
Everyone′s got so much to say
I always feel like I am nobody‚ mm
Who wants to fit in anyway?
′Cause I don′t care when I
am with my baby‚ yeah
All the bad things disappear
And You are making me feel
like maybe I am somebody
I can deal with the bad nights
When I am with my baby‚ yeah
′Cause I don′t care as long
as you just hold me near
You can take me anywhere
And You are making me feel like
I am loved by somebody
I can deal with the bad nights
When I am with my baby‚ yeah
We at a party we don′t wanna be at
Tryna talk‚ but we can′t
hear ourselves
Press your lips‚ I had rather
kiss them right back
With all these people all around
I am crippled with anxiety
But I am told It is where
I am supposed to be
You know what? It is kinda crazy
′cause I really don′t mind
When you make it better like that
Don′t think we fit in at this party
Everyone′s got so much to
say‚ oh yeah‚ yeah
When we walked in‚ I said
I am sorry‚ mm
But now I think that we should stay
′Cause I don′t care when I
am with my baby‚ yeah
All the bad things disappear
Yeah‚ You are making me feel
like maybe I am somebody
I can deal with the bad nights
when I am with my baby‚ yeah
′Cause I don′t care as long
as you just hold me near
You can take me anywhere
And You are making me feel like
I am loved by somebody
I can deal with the bad nights
When I am with my baby‚ yeah
I don′t like nobody but you‚ It is
like You are the only one here
I don′t like nobody but you‚
baby‚ I don′t care
I hate everyone here
I don′t like nobody but
you‚ baby‚ yeah
′Cause I don′t care (Don′t care)
When I am with my baby‚ yeah
All the bad things disappear
(Disappear)
And You are making me feel
like maybe I am somebody
(Maybe I am somebody)
I can deal with the bad nights
(With the bad nights)
When I am with my baby‚ yeah
′Cause I don′t care as long as you
just hold me near (Me near)
You can take me anywhere
(Anywhere‚ anywhere)
And You are making me feel like
I am loved by somebody
I can deal with the bad nights
When I am with my baby‚ yeah
by RentAnAdviser.com