by RentAnAdviser.com
Thought I found a way
Thought I found a way out (out)
But you never go away (never go away)
So I guess I gotta stay now
Oh I hope someday I will
make it out of here
Even if it takes all night
or a hundred years
Need a place to hide but
I can′t find one near
Wanna feel alive outside
I can′t fight my fear
Isn′t it lovely?
All alone
Heart made of glass my mind of stone
Tear me to pieces
Skin to bone
Hello
Welcome home
Walking out of time
Looking for a better place
Something′s on my mind
(Mind)
Always in my head space
But I know someday I will
make it out of here
Even if it takes all night
or a hundred years
Need a place to hide but
I can′t find one near
Wanna feel alive outside
I can′t fight my fear
Isn′t it lovely?
All alone
Heart made of glass my mind of stone
Tear me to pieces
Skin to bone
Hello
Welcome home
Hello‚ welcome home
by RentAnAdviser.com