by RentAnAdviser.com
Needless to say‚ I keep in check
She was all bad bad‚ nevertheless
Callin′ it quit is now‚ baby‚
I am a wreck (wreck)
Crash at my place‚ baby‚ You
are a wreck (wreck)
Needless to say‚ I am keepin′ in check
She was all bad bad‚ nevertheless
Callin′ it quit is now‚
baby‚ I am a wreck
Crash at my place‚ baby‚
You are a wreck
Thinkin′ in a bad way‚
losin′ your grip
Screamin′ at my face‚ baby don′t trip
Someone took a big L‚ don′t
know how that felt
Lookin′ at you sideways‚ party on tilt
Ooh ooh‚ some things you
just can′t refuse
She wanna ride me like a cruise
And I am not tryna lose
And You are left in the dust
Unless I stuck by ya
You are a sunflower
I think your love would be too much
Or you′ll be left in the dust
Unless I stuck by ya
You are the sunflower
Every time I am leavin′ on ya
You don′t make it easy‚ no‚ no
Wish I could be there for ya
Give me a reason to go
Every time I am walkin′ out
I can hear you tellin′
me to turn around
Fightin′ for my trust and
you won′t back down
Even if we gotta risk it
all right now‚ oh
I know You are scared of the unknown
You don′t wanna be alone (alone)
I know I always come and go (and go)
But It is out of my control
And you′ll be left in the dust
Unless I stuck by ya
You are a sunflower
I think your love would be too much
Or you′ll be left in the dust
Unless I stuck by ya
You are the sunflower
by RentAnAdviser.com