by RentAnAdviser.com
We couldn′t turn around ′til
we were upside down
I will be the bad guy now‚ but
know I ain′t too proud
I couldn′t be there even when I tried
You don′t believe it‚ we
do this every time
Seasons change and our love went cold
Feed the flame ′cause we can′t let go
Run away‚ but We are
running in circles
Run away‚ run away
I dare you to do something
I am waiting on you again‚ so
I don′t take the blame
Run away‚ but We are
running in circles
Run away‚ run away‚ run away
Let go‚ I got a feeling that
It is time to let go
I said so‚ I knew that this was
doomed from the get go
You thought that it was
special‚ special
But it was just the sex though‚
the sex though
And I still hear the echoes
(The echoes)
I got a feeling that It is time
to let it go‚ let it go
Seasons change and our love went cold
Feed the flame ′cause we can′t let go
Run away‚ but We are
running in circles
Run away‚ run away
I dare you to do something
I am waiting on you again‚ so
I don′t take the blame
Run away‚ but We are
running in circles
Run away‚ run away‚ run away
Maybe you don′t understand
what I am going through
It is only me‚ what you got to lose?
Make up your mind‚ tell me‚
what are you gona do?
It is only me‚ let it go
Seasons change and our love went cold
Feed the flame ′cause we can′t let go
Run away‚ but We are
running in circles
Run away‚ run away
I dare you to do something
I am waiting on you again‚ so
I don′t take the blame
Run away‚ but We are
running in circles
Run away‚ run away‚ run away
by RentAnAdviser.com