by RentAnAdviser.com
Lately I have been thinking
I want you to be happier
When the morning come
When we see what we′ve become
In the cold light of day
We are a flame in the wind not
the fire that we′ve begun
Every argument
Every word we can′t take back
Cause with all that has happened
I think that we both know
the way that story ends
Then only for a minute
I want to change my mind
Cause this just don′t feel right to me
I wanna raise your spirit is
I want to see you smile
Know that means I will have to leave
Lately I have been thinking
I want you to be happier
When the evevning falls
And I am left there with my thougts
And the image of you being
with someone else
Well It is eating me up inside
But we ran our course
We pretended We are okay
Now if we jump together
At least we can swing far away
from the wreck we made
Then only for a minute
I want to change my mind
Cause this just don′t feel right to me
I wanna raise your spirit is
I want to see you smile
Know that means I will have to leave
Lately I have been thinking
I want you to be happier
So I will go
I will go
I will go go go
So I will go
I will go
Lately I have been thinking
I want you to be happier
Even though I might not like this
I think that you′ll be happier
I want you to be happier
Then only for a minute
I want to change my mind
Cause this just don′t feel right to me
I wanna raise your spirit is
I want to see you smile
Know that means I will have to leave
Lately I have been thinking
I want you to be happier
So I will go
I will go
I will go go go
by RentAnAdviser.com