by RentAnAdviser.com
Yeah‚ I am gona take my horse
to the old town road
I am gona ride ′til I can′t no more
I am gona take my horse
to the old town road
I am gona ride ′til I can′t no more
I got the horses in the back
Horse tack is attached
Hat is matte black
Got the boots that′s black to match
Ridin′ on a horse‚ ha
You can whip your Porsche
I been in the valley
You ain′t been up off that porch‚ now
Can′t nobody tell me nothin′
You can′t tell me nothin′
Ridin′ on a tractor
Lean all in my bladder
Cheated on my baby
You can go and ask her
My life is a movie
Bull ridin′ and boobies
Cowboy hat from Gucci
Wrangler on my booty
Can′t nobody tell me nothin′
You can′t tell me nothin′
Yeah‚ I am gona take my horse
to the old town road
I am gona ride ′til I can′t no more
I am gona take my horse
to the old town road
I am gona ride ′til I can′t no more
Hat down‚ cross town‚ livin′
like a rockstar
Spent a lot of money on
my brand new guitar
Baby′s got a habit‚ diamond rings
and Fendi sports bras
Ridin′ down Rodeo in my
Maserati sports car
Got no stress‚ I have been
through all that
I am like a Marlboro man
so I kick on back
Wish I could roll on back
to that old town road
I wanna ride ′til I can′t no more
Yeah‚ I am gona take my horse
to the old town road
I am gona ride ′til I can′t no more
I am gona take my horse
to the old town road
I am gona ride ′til I can′t no more
by RentAnAdviser.com