by RentAnAdviser.com
I have been reading books of old
The legends and the myths
Achilles and his gold
Hercules and his gifts
Spiderman′s control
And Batman with his fists
And clearly I don′t see
myself upon that list
But she said‚ where′d you wanna go?
How much you wanna risk?
I am not looking for somebody
With some superhuman gifts
Some superhero
Some fairytale bliss
Just something I can turn to
Somebody I can kiss
I want something just like this
Doo doo doo‚ doo doo doo
Oh‚ I want something just like this
I want something just like this
Doo doo doo‚ doo doo doo
I have been reading books of old
The legends and the myths
The testaments they told
The moon and it is eclipse
And Superman unrolls
A suit before he lifts
But I am not the kind of
person that it fit is
She said‚ where′d you wanna go?
How much you wanna risk?
I am not looking for somebody
With some superhuman gifts
Some superhero
Some fairytale bliss
Just something I can turn to
Somebody I can miss
I want something just like this
Doo doo doo‚ doo doo doo
Oh‚ I want something just like this
by RentAnAdviser.com