by RentAnAdviser.com
Loving can hurt‚ loving
can hurt sometimes
But It is the only thing that I know
When it gets hard‚ you know
it can get hard sometimes
It is the only thing that
makes us feel alive
We keep this love in a photograph
We made these memories for ourselves
Where our eyes are never closing
Hearts are never broken
And time′s forever frozen still
So you can keep me
Inside the pocket of your ripped jeans
Holding me closer ′til our eyes met
You won′t ever be alone‚ wait
for me to come home
Loving can heal‚ loving
can mend your soul
And It is the only thing
that I know‚ know
I swear it will get easier
Remember that with every piece of you
Hm‚ and It is the only thing we
take with us when we die
Hm‚ we keep this love
in this photograph
We made these memories for ourselves
Where our eyes are never closing
Hearts were never broken
And time′s forever frozen still
So you can keep me
Inside the pocket of your ripped jeans
Holding me closer ′til our eyes met
You won′t ever be alone
And if you hurt me
That′s okay baby‚ only words bleed
Inside these pages you just hold me
And I won′t ever let you go
Wait for me to come home
You can fit me
Inside the necklace you got
when you were sixteen
Next to your heartbeat
where I should be
Keep it deep within your soul
And if you hurt me
Well‚ that′s okay baby‚
only words bleed
Inside these pages you just hold me
And I won′t ever let you go
When I am away‚ I will remember
how you kissed me
Under the lamppost back
on Sixth street
Hearing you whisper through the phone
Wait for me to come home.
www.RentAnAdviser.com