by RentAnAdviser.com
I should have known
I had leave alone
Just goes to show
That the blood you bleed is
just the blood you owe
We were a pair
But I saw you there
Too much to bear
You were my life‚ but life
is far away from fair
Was I stupid to love you?
Was I reckless to help?
Was it obvious to everybody else?
That I had fallen for a lie
You were never on my side
Fool me once‚ fool me twice
Are you death or paradise?
Now you′ll never see me cry
There′s just no time to die
I let it burn
You are no longer my concern
Faces from my past return
Another lesson yet to learn
That I had fallen for a lie
You were never on my side
Fool me once‚ fool me twice
Are you death or paradise?
Now you′ll never see me cry
There′s just no time to die
No time to die
No time to die‚ ooh
Fool me once‚ fool me twice
Are you death or paradise?
Now you′ll never see me cry
There′s just no time to die
by RentAnAdviser.com