by RentAnAdviser.com
Spent 24 hours‚ I need
more hours with you
You spent the weekend
getting even‚ ooh
We spent the late nights making
things right between us
But now It is all good‚ baby
Roll that back wood‚ baby
And play me close
′Cause girls like you run ′round
with guys like me
′Til sun down when I come through
I need a girl like you‚ yeah yeah
Girls like you love fun‚
and yeah‚ me too
What I want when I come through
I need a girl like you‚ yeah yeah
Yeah yeah yeah‚ yeah yeah yeah
I need a girl like you
I spent last night on the
last flight to you
Took a whole day up tryna
get way up‚ ooh
We spent the daylight tryna make
things right between us
But now It is all good‚ baby
Roll that back wood‚ baby
And play me close
′Cause girls like you run ′round
with guys like me
′Til sun down when I come through
I need a girl like you‚ yeah yeah
Girls like you love fun‚
and yeah‚ me too
What I want when I come through
I need a girl like you‚ yeah yeah
Yeah yeah yeah‚ yeah yeah yeah
I need a girl like you
Maybe It is 6:45
Maybe I am barely alive
Maybe You have taken my shit
for the last time‚ yeah
Maybe I know that I am drunk
Maybe I know You are the one
Maybe You are thinking It
is better if you drive
Oh ′cause girls like you run
′round with guys like me
′Til sun down when I come through
I need a girl like you‚ yeah
Not too long ago I was
dancin′ for dollars
Knew it was really real if
I let you met my momma
You don′t want a girl like
me I am too crazy
But every other girl you met is fugazy
I am sure them other girls
were nice enough
But you need someone to spice it up
So who you gona call cardi cardi
To come and rev it up like
a harley harley
Why is the best fruit always forbidden
I am coming to you now doin′
20 over the limit
The red light red light stop (stop)
I don′t play when it comes to my
heart‚ lets get it though
I don′t really want a white
horse and a carriage
I am thinking more white
porsches and karats
I need you right here cause
every time you fall
I play with this kitty like
you play wit your guitar
′Cause girls like you run ′round
with guys like me
′Til sun down when I come through
I need a girl like you‚ yeah yeah
Girls like you love fun‚
and yeah‚ me too
What I want when I come through
I need a girl like you‚ yeah yeah
Yeah yeah yeah‚ yeah yeah yeah
I need a girl like you
by RentAnAdviser.com