by RentAnAdviser.com
I have been tryna call
I have been on my own for long enough
Maybe you can show me
how to love‚ maybe
I am going through withdrawals
You don′t even have to do too much
You can turn me on with
just a touch‚ baby
I look around and
Sin City′s cold and empty
No one′s around to judge me
I can′t see clearly when You are gone
I said‚ ooh‚ I am blinded
by the lights
No‚ I can′t sleep until
I feel your touch
I said‚ ooh‚ I am drowning
in the night
Oh‚ when I am like this‚ You
are the one I trust
Hey‚ hey‚ hey
I am running out of time
′Cause I can see the sun
light up the sky
So I hit the road in overdrive‚
baby‚ oh
The city′s cold and empty
No one′s around to judge me
I can′t see clearly when You are gone
I said‚ ooh‚ I am blinded
by the lights
No‚ I can′t sleep until
I feel your touch
I said‚ ooh‚ I am drowning
in the night
Oh‚ when I am like this‚ You
are the one I trust
I am just calling back to let you
know (Back to let you know)
I could never say it on the phone
(Say it on the phone)
Will never let you go this time
I said‚ ooh‚ I am blinded
by the lights
No‚ I can′t sleep until
I feel your touch
Hey‚ hey‚ hey
I said‚ ooh‚ I am blinded
by the lights
No‚ I can′t sleep until
I feel your touch
by RentAnAdviser.com