by RentAnAdviser.com
Walk in your rainbow paradise
(Paradise)
Strawberry lipstick state
of mind (State of mind)
I get so lost inside your eyes
Would you believe it?
You don′t have to say you love me
You don′t have to say nothing
You don′t have to say You are mine
Honey
I had walk through fire for you
Just let me adore you
Oh‚ honey
I had walk through fire for you
Just let me adore you
Like It is the only thing
I will ever do
You are wonder under summer
sky (Summer sky)
Brown skin and lemon over ice
Would you believe it?
You don′t have to say you love me
I just wanna tell you somethin′
Lately‚ You have been on my mind
Honey
I had walk through fire for you
Just let me adore you
Oh‚ honey
I had walk through fire for you
Just let me adore you
Like It is the only thing
I will ever do
It is the only thing I will ever do
I had walk through fire for you
Just let me adore you
Oh‚ honey
I had walk through fire for you
Just let me adore you
Like It is the only thing
I will ever do
I had walk through fire for you (It
is the only thing I will ever do)
Just let me adore you
Oh‚ honey ‚ oh‚ honey
I had walk through fire for you (It
is the only thing I will ever do)
Just let me adore you (It is the
only thing I will ever do)
Just let me adore you
Like It is the only thing
I will ever do
by RentAnAdviser.com